7/31/23, 9:16 AM InfoJobs - CV

# InfoJobs

Por leer en Native English - US Market - Business Development Representative (B2B)



# Business Development associate en Mithril Security

CV actualizado el 17/07/2023

Edad: 27 años (14/02/1996)

✓ Tú pides: Madrid

Madrid

Vehículo propio: No

Autónomo: No

Género: Hombre

# Killer questions

### Tell us about your experience of working on the phone, please.

I have 2 years of experience doing cold calling in the Argentinian market, selling spray and cream actuators to the cosmetics, medical and perfumery sectors. Resulting in a 1.000% growth in sales in less than 6 months.



## Experiencias

Septiembre 2022 - Actualmente (10 meses)

# **Business Development associate**

Mithril Security | Servicios y tecnología de la información

Privacy - Terms

7/31/23, 9:16 AM InfoJobs - CV

- Part of the business development team, searching and contacting leads, for market research and sales purposes.

- I am helping Mithril Security with market research, creating the sales funnel, and working with the CRM to keep track of all the campaigns and leads.
- Working with different prospection and messaging tools.
- Helping the whole team on different tasks, from content creation, website construction, admin tasks, etc.

Salario 30.000 € - 33.000 € Bruto/año

Nivel Empleado/a

Categoría y subcategoría Comercial y ventas: Agente comercial

Office 365 LaGrowthMachine Apollo Hubspot LinkedIn Meet Alfred Waalaxy Notion

Marzo 2022 - Agosto 2022 (5 meses)

## **Business development & Sales**

Tyfast Energy | Fabric. prod. informáticos, electrónicos y ópticos

Nivel Becario/a - Prácticas

Categoría y subcategoría Comercial y ventas: Agente comercial, Comercial

Generación de Leads B2B Desarrollo de negocio Business development

Diciembre 2015 - Noviembre 2017 (1 año y 11 meses)

## Vendedor/a

Bombas vaporizadoras S.R.L | Importación y exportación

Vendedor de insumos para la industria cosmética, farmacéutica y de limpieza.

Nivel Becario/a - Prácticas

Categoría y subcategoría Comercial y ventas: Televenta y marketing telefónico

CRM (Customer Relationship

Management)

### **Estudios**

Estudios reglados

GRADO

Septiembre 2018 - Actualmente (4 años y 10 meses)

## Grado en Administración y Dirección de Empresas

Universidad Europea de Madrid

### Idiomas

Francés

Básico

7/31/23, 9:16 AM InfoJobs - CV

Inglés

Avanzado